WESTERN Province

RUSIZI District

Email: impanomanzienock@gmail.com

Phone: +250791105800

20th march 2024

To the General President Director of INYANGE Industries

PO Box 87 Kigali

RE: Applying for job vacant (assistant project manager)

I would like to write this letter for request job of being assistant project manager at INYANGE Industries, as advertised on social media.

In fact, I am Rwandan, aged with 22 years old I have bachelor's degree in project management from Makerere University with 3 years' experience in that position currently, I am project manager at Muhabura mining factory. Because of that background and experience that is the main reason why I am applying for that job vacant.

In attachment on this letter, you will find all other required documents. If you need more information, you could reach me on contact I provided in my CV.

I am hearing forward from you.

Yours Sincerely,

IMPANO MANZI Enock

CURRICULMN VITAE

CONTACT DETAILS

Names: IMPANO MANZI Enock

Date of birth: 17 September 2024

Location: Rusizi District, Kamembe Sector

Phone:250791105800

Email: impanomanzienock@gmail.com

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

YEAR	SCHOOL	OPTION	AWARD
2018-2022	University of Rwanda	Project management	Bachelor's Degree
2015-2017	Groupe scolaire notre dame de la paix Cyanika	Business services	Advance TVT certificate
2006-2011	Ecole primaire	Primary school	Primary school
	Gihundwe	studies	certificate

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2021- September 2021: Internship at Rwanda plastic industry

2023-Now: Project Manager at Muhabura Mining Factory

LANGUAGES

LANGUAGE	WRITING	READING	LISTENING
Kinyarwanda	best	best	best
English	best	best	best
Kiswahili	good	good	good
French	good	good	good

SKILLS AND ACHIEVEMENT

SKILLS

1. Microsoft office Word, PowerPoint, publisher, excel

- 2. Graphical design
- 3. Software and web development
- 4. Communication skills

ACHIEVEMENTS

In 2023, I awarded as best employee of the year at Muhabura mining factory

INTEREST

- 1. Playing chess
- 2. Teaching

REFERENCES

NAMES	POSITION	COMPANY	PHONE	EMAIL
SIBOMANA	Human	Muhabura	25078	sinm@gmail.com
Samuel	Resource	mining factory		
	Manager			
ISHIMWE	Lecturer	University of	250788	clement@gmail.com
Clement		Rwanda		
Musafiri innocent	Internership	Rwanda	2578	Mus129@gmail.com
	supervisor	plastic		
		industry		

I testify that the above information are real and concerns me and can be verified

IMPANO MANZI Enock